http://www.polandbymail.com/h/51/privacy-policy.htm

Privacy Policy
at Polart - PolandByMail
Polart - Poland By Mail
FREE SHIPPING*On Orders Over $85
This offer is only applicable to orders placed online that ship within the continental United States.
Login My Account View Basket Checkout
For The Home Media Clothing Collectibles Children Holiday Other
GO
For The Home
Home Decor Boxes & Plates Bronze & Brass Decorative Candles & Holders Games, Puzzles, & Chess Sets Glass & Ceramic Vases & Bowls Glasses, Mugs, & Accessories Home Accessories Kitchen Accessories Office Products Steins & Accessories Wooden Decorations
Wall Decor Silver Plated Icons Photo Prints Posters Signs Wall Hangings Silkscreen Prints Folk Arts Dolls Nesting Dolls Highlanders Russian Products Walking Canes & Ciupagi
Polish Pottery Mugs Crystal Products Holistic Remedies
Media
Books Audio Books (Clearance) Books in English Books in Polish Language Learning Maps & Atlases Administrative Maps Area Maps City Plan Maps City PLUS Maps Military Maps Interwar Maps of Poland (1918-1939) Regional Maps Specialty Maps & Atlases Tourist Maps Wall Maps
Calendars Movies: DVDs & VCDs Action Films on DVD Comedies on DVD Dramas on DVD Romances on DVD Historical Films on DVD Pre-1939 Classics WWII Films on DVD Music, Travel & Documentary on DVD Children's Films on DVD Children's Films on VCD Boxed DVD & VCD Sets Greeting Cards & Stationary
Music: CD & VCD Karaoke Sets - Two CDs or More Blues & Jazz Cabaret & Poetry Children's Music Classical & Organ Easy Listening Folk Music Holiday Music Patriotic Music Platinum Collection Polka & Dance Pop & Rock Religious Soundtracks Various Karaoke VCD Audio Cassettes
Clothing
Adult Cotton Tees Women's Cotton Tees Long Sleeve Adult Tees Crew Neck Sweatshirts Hooded Sweatshirts Caps & Hats, Scarves & Socks Slippers & Shoes Athletic Wear, Jackets & More Bags Accessories Adult Suspenders Toddler Suspenders
Collectibles
The Mint of Poland Gold Medals Silver Medals Gold Plated Silver Medals Gold & Silver Medal Sets Jewelry Gold & Silver Jewelry Amber Jewelry Wooden & Other Jewelry Italian Charms Lapel Pins Tie Clips Military Memorabilia Armor, Swords & Weapons Czapkas Historical Headware Handcrafted Military Figures Model Kits & Other Collectables Warsaw Pact Memorabilia
Flags, Mementos, Collectibles Bags Bells Bottle Openers Coins, Stamps & Medals Collectible Spoons Figures & Sculptures Flags & Car Accessories Ink Pens Keychains Lapel Pins Lanyards & Bracelets Letter Openers Magnets Patches Stickers & Buttons Thimbles Tie Clips Religious Products Pope John Paul II Figures & Crosses Icons & Wall Decor Jewelry & Rosary Boxes Religious Accessories
Children
Children's Items Toys & Games Children's Cotton Tees Children's Books in English Children's Books in Polish Bilingual Comic Books Coloring Books Films with dialogues in Polish on DVD Films without or limited dialogues in Polish on DVD Films, Lullabies, & Karaoke on VCD Music & Stories for Children on CD
Holiday
Polish Christmas Christmas Gifts Gifts for Her Gifts for Him Gifts for Kids Christmas Books Christmas Carols Karaoke Carols Greeting Cards Ornaments Straw Decorations
Wooden Butter Molds Polish Easter Easter Gifts Easter Eggs Easter Music Easter Books Easter Greeting Cards
Clearance Other
Products with Free Shipping - USA only New Arrivals One-of-a-Kind Sale Items - Clearance Savings Bundles Send Flowers to Poland Periodical Subscriptions
Your current browser does not have JavaScript enabled or you are using a browser that does not support JavaScript. In order to use this site you must enable JavaScript or use a browser that supports JavaScript.1-800-278-9393Contact UsProduct DirectoryFor The HomeMediaClothingCollectiblesChildren's ItemsHolidayOtherJoin Our Newsletterand Get 10% OFFyour next order!
Follow Us On
Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy(For Information Only)Our Commitment to PrivacyOur Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs. What Information Do We Collect?When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.Personal Information You Choose to ProvideCredit Card Information If you choose to purchase products or services from us, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:Name Mailing address Email address Credit card number Home and business phone number Other personal information Email InformationIn addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.Web Site Use InformationSimilar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers? personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers.What Are Cookies? Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user?s Web browser on the user?s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user?s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users? browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers.Sharing Information with AffiliatesFrom time to time you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our Web site. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies.Sharing Information with Strategic PartnersWe may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties who may be given access to selected information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information, and we will not share information regarding provided phone numbers, or other personal financial data. Notice of New Services and ChangesOccasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our client, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on a response box when you receive such an offer.How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?When you send confidential personal credit card information to us on our Web site, a secure server software which we have licensed encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. The information is scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches our Web site.Other email that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an unsecured email. How Do We Protect Your Information?Information Security. We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.Evaluation of Information Protection Practices. Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information.Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.
Home Contact Us Testimonials Order Form
Size Charts Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Site Map
Professional Ecommerce Services By GlobalWebCart Ecommerce Shopping Cart Software
